<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UNS</string>
    <string name="about_university_title">
        MODERN UNIVERSITY THAT CONSISTS OF FOURTEEN FACULTIES IN FOUR HISTORIC CITIES OF CENTRAL EUROPE
    </string>
    <string name="about_university">
        The University of Novi Sad has more than 50.000 students and 5.000 employees and as such it is one of the largest educational and research centres in Central Europe. It belongs to the group of universities that provide a broad range of comprehensive and up-to date knowledge of almost all scientific areas.\n\n
The University of Novi Sad offers 300 accredited study programmes on all study levels, undergraduate, master, specialist and doctoral studies, which are carried out on the Faculties and University Centres for Interdisciplinary and Multidisciplinary Studies. All study programmes are modern and in accordance with the development of science. Apart from the Faculties and Centres, two Scientific Institutes have an important role in creating a firm scientific base for the continuous modernization of these study programmes.\n\n
The University of Novi Sad has a well developed scientific infrastructure and an enormous innovative potential. The Central Library and the Faculty and Institute Libraries have rich literary collections that cover all relevant scientific areas and enable access to big electronic databases. As a result of a special agreement on cooperation, researchers, professors and students have access to the Matica Srpska Library, the oldest Serbian scientific and cultural institution, founded in 1826, and which has more than 3 million publications. There are several up-to-date laboratories. The Technology Park of the University of Novi Sad has special significance for the development of innovative ideas.\n\n
As a result of such infrastructure and the quality of scientific and educational work, high results were achieved in some areas.\n\n
With the support of the Faculty of Technical Sciences and other members of the University, 125 start-up and spin-off companies were founded, mostly in the IT sector, which employ young engineers who graduated from the University of Novi Sad. Some of these companies carry out projects for big international companies and they have contributed to the recognition of Novi Sad as the “Software Valley” in the international circles. Project teams and distinguished researchers from the University have received numerous international and national awards for the best technological innovations.\n\n
The University of Novi Sad is well-known for the accredited centres of excellence in the fields of mathematics, vibro-acoustics and biotechnology. BioSense Institute, which was founded within the Faculty of Technical Sciences was proclaimed to be one of the thirty research institutions in Europe with the greatest potential in the field of biotechnologies.\n\n
The students of the Faculty of Sport and Physical Education have been achieving impressive results for decades in international competitions, and the students of the Faculty of Law are among the best in the European moot court competitions. Among the best in Europe are also the students’ teams of the Faculty of Technical sciences in competitions in robotics.\n\n
The University of Novi Sad connects people, space and time. Its Faculties and Institutes are situated in four historic cities in the Autonomous Province of Vojvodina, in the north of the Republic of Serbia.\n\n
The headquarters of the University of Novi Sad are in Novi Sad, in the central campus on the bank of the Danube, near the famous Petrovaradin fortress, built in the 18th century, as well as in the vicinity of the old city centre. The following Faculties are also situated there: Faculty of Philosophy, Faculty of Agriculture, Faculty of Sciences, Faculty of Law, Faculty of Technical Sciences, Faculty of Technology, Faculty of Sport and Physical Education and the Institute of Food Technology, as well as the Department of the Faculty of Economics, headquartered in Subotica. Faculty of Medicine, Academy of Arts and the Institute of Lowland Forestry and the Environment are situated in other parts of the city for practical purposes.\n\n
In Subotica, there are Faculty of Economics, Faculty of Civil Engineering, and the Teachers’ Training Faculty in the Hungarian Language. The headquarters of the Faculty of Education are in Sombor and that of the Technical Faculty “Mihajlo Pupin” are in Zrenjanin. All these institutions are accredited and they have valid licences to work.\n\n
The students of the University of Novi Sad have at their disposal special services that provide healthcare, accommodation and food. Medical services are provided by the Health Protection Centre, which comprises units for specialist health care, medical counseling and laboratories. Accommodation and food are provided by the Student Centre. The level of services that are provided is in accordance with the standards accepted in the developed European countries.\n\n
The University of Novi Sad builds its future together with other institutions that belong to the unique European scientific and educational community, but it also actively cooperates with other institutions from all over the world. This cooperation is based on many bilateral and multilateral agreements that ensure collaboration on joint research and development projects, mobility of students, teaching and administrative staff, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="about_application_title">
        O APLIKACIJI
    </string>
    <string name="about_application">
        Mobile application which is able to provide necessary information to students and employees. Using this application you are able to find all relevant places and information related to campus.Feel free to contribute, project is open source, and it is available on: https://github.com/unsftn/unsmobile.\n\nIt is developed by Aleksandar Bosnjak and Nenad Todorovic.\nChairs of Informatics.\nElectrical and computing department.\nFaculty Of Technical Sciences, University Of Novi Sad.\n

        \n\n
        2017©. Sva prava rezervisana. Univerzitet u Novom Sadu.
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Podešavanja</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bus_routes">University bus routes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notable_locations">Važne lokacije</string>
    <string name="route">Ruta</string>
    <string name="title_activity_science_festival">ScienceFestivalActivity</string>
    <string name="title_university">Univerzitet</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_application">Aplikacija</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_people">Adresar</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">O nama</string>
    <string name="english_localization">English</string>
    <string name="serbian_localization">Srpski</string>
    <string name="bus_routes_headline_title">Related bus route numbers:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faculties">UNS fakulteti</string>
    <string name="ftn_title">Fakultet tehničkih nauka</string>
    <string name="pmf_title">Prirodno-matematički fakultet</string>
    <string name="law_title">Pravni fakultet</string>
    <string name="agriculture_title">Poljoprivredni fakultet</string>
    <string name="philosophy_title">Filozofski fakultet</string>
    <string name="economics_title">Ekonomski fakultet</string>
    <string name="technology_title">Tehnološki fakultet</string>
    <string name="medicine_title">Medicinski fakultet</string>
    <string name="art_academy_title">Akademija umetnosti</string>
    <string name="civil_engineering_title">Građevinski fakultet</string>
    <string name="pupin_title">Tehnički fakultet „Mihajlo Pupin”</string>
    <string name="dif_title">Fakultet sporta i fizičkog vaspitanja</string>
    <string name="education_title">Pedagoški fakultet</string>
    <string name="open_bus_routes_map">Open bus routes map</string>
    <string name="faculties">Fakulteti</string>
    <string name="bus_routes">Bus routes</string>
    <string name="notable_locations">Notable locations</string>
    <string name="dormitories">Studentski domovi</string>
    <string name="people">Raja</string>
    <string name="libraries">Libraries</string>
    <string name="dining">Dining</string>
    <string name="science_festival">Science festival</string>
    <string name="links">Links</string>
    <string name="full_website">Full website</string>
    <string name="about">O nama</string>
    <string name="_2017_uns_novi_sad_serbia">"2017 © UNS\nNovi Sad, Srbija\nUNSinfo@uns.ac.rs"</string>

    <string name="rectory_title">UNS Rektorat</string>
    <string name="rectory_desc">Rektorat Univerziteta u Novom Sadu</string>

    <string name="address_book_header">Pretražite kontakte osoblja univerziteta.</string>
    <string name="address_book_text">
        <![CDATA[
            <html>
             <head></head>
             <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;font-size:18;">
              Broj centrale: (+381 21) 485-2000<br/>
              Svim brojevima lokala sa telefonske
              centrale Univerziteta, osim lokala
              koji počinju cifrom 5, može se
              direktno pristupiti dodavanjem
              prefiksa 485 ispred broja lokala.
             </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="i_blank"> -- Svi fakulteti -- </string>
    <string name="i_university">Univerzitet u Novom Sadu</string>
    <string name="i_pmf">Prirodno-matematički fakultet</string>
    <string name="i_ftn">Fakultet tehničkih nauka</string>
    <string name="i_ff">Filozofski fakultet</string>
    <string name="i_pf">Pravni fakultet</string>
    <string name="i_efns">Ekonomski fakultet - odelenje Novi Sad</string>
    <string name="i_pof">Poljoprivredni fakultet</string>
    <string name="i_tf">Tehnološki fakultet</string>
    <string name="i_efsu">Ekonomski fakultet - Subotica</string>
    <string name="i_ipt">Institut za prehrambene tehnologije</string>
    <string name="i_edu_hun">Učiteljski fakultet na Mađarskom jeziku</string>
    <string name="i_spinner_prompt">Institution</string>

    <string name="wp_blank"> -- Sva zanimanja -- </string>
    <string name="wp_administrative"> Administrativni radnik </string>
    <string name="wp_administrator"> Administrator </string>
    <string name="wp_spinner_prompt">Zanimanje</string>
    <string name="insert_a_name">Insert a name</string>
    <string name="insert_a_surname">Insert a surname</string>
    <string name="search_people">Search</string>

    <string name="people_form_empty_message">Nothing to search by!</string>
</resources>
